lorextechnology.com 2011-12-11

# Privacy Policy LOREX | LOREX TECHNOLOGY INC. | Wired Products - CCTV Security Observation Systems, Security Cameras, Surveillance DVRs

**LorexTechnology.com Statement of Privacy**

_last updated April 24, 2006_

This Privacy Policy covers the following URL's;

At Lorex Technology, we are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of Lorex Technology; it does not apply to other online or offline Lorex Technoogy sites, products or services. Please read the complete Lorex Technology privacy statement.

**Collecting your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are registering before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, signing up for an event, or when purchasing and registering Lorex Technology products. Personal information collected by Lorex Technology often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

For example: If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase in the shopping area of the Web site, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number.

When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. When you do, we keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site. This is considered your personal profile.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.
  * To deliver services that you request or purchase.
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Lorex Technology may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Lorex Technology or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Lorex Technology and its family of Web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Lorex Technology, its Web sites, or the public.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Lorex Technology or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Lorex Technology abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the Canadian Ministry of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Control of your Personal Information**  
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, www.lorextechnology.com will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

Registering also allows you to tell us how or whether you want www.lorextechnology.com to communicate with you.

www.lorextechnology.com occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services, using postal mail only.

www.lorextechnology.com may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service issues related to a product or service you requested. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen.

**Access to your Personal Information**  
We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time by contacting us at info@www.lorextechnology.com. You can:

View and edit personal information you have already given us at www.lorextechnology.com.   
Tell us whether you want www.lorextechnology.com to send you marketing information.   
Choose whether you want third parties to send you their offers by postal mail.   
Subscribe, or cancel subscriptions, to newsletters about our services and products.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
www.lorextechnology.com strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your login and password, so do not share these with others.

**Protection of Children's Personal Information**  
The www.lorextechnology.com site does not publish content that is targeted to children.

**Use of Cookies**  
To ensure we are publishing content customers need and want, www.lorextechnology.com collects site-visitation statistics using cookies. We only use this information in aggregated form and only use site-visitation statistics for improving our site.

When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously.

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the www.lorextechnology.com Web site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site. Your Shopping Cart will also not remember items added but not checked out.

**Changes to this Statement**  
www.lorextechnology.com will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, www.lorextechnology.com will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.

**Contact Information**  
Lorex Technology welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us at [info@lorextechnology.com](mailto:info@lorextechnology.com).
